So we've talked about a common household chore doing laundry.
所以我们谈到了洗衣服的常见家务。
Now let's talk about an errand I mentioned we would talk about errands.
现在让我们谈谈我提到的一个差事，我们将讨论差事。
Things that we have to do things that we plan to do usually before we go out.
我们必须做的事情 我们通常在外出之前就计划做的事情。
And these are usually things that are fairly quick they don't last a long time.
这些通常是相当快的事情，它们不会持续很长时间。
And we have to go out to do them.
我们必须出去做。
We don't do them at home.
我们不在家里做。
They're not chores although they're similar to chores in the sense that they're kind of daily things.
它们不是家务，尽管它们与家务相似，因为它们是日常事务。
Things we usually need to do.
我们通常需要做的事情。
There are a couple of common or a few common phrases that we can use when we're describing errands.
当我们描述差事时，我们可以使用几个常见的或几个常用的短语。
When we're talking about errands I want to make sure they're clear.
当我们谈论差事时，我想确保它们是清楚的。
Number one pickup pickup means to get.
第一皮卡皮卡意味着得到。
Same as get.
和得到一样。
Sometimes it means by sometimes it means take something away from.
有时它意味着有时它意味着带走一些东西。
So we might pick up some bread from the supermarket.
所以我们可能会去超市买些面包。
Of course you're picking it up but we often use pickup for a lot of different things to mean get which
当然你是在捡起它，但我们经常用pickup来表示很多不同的事情，意思是得到哪个
could include buying or maybe not because you could say I need to pick up my friend from the train station.
可能包括购买或不购买，因为您可以说我需要从火车站接我的朋友。
Does that mean you need to pick them up.
这是否意味着您需要接他们。
No you're going to drive to the train station.
不，你要开车去火车站。
Wait and then they're maybe going to get in the car with you pick up my friend at the airport pick up
等等，然后他们可能会和你一起上车接我的朋友在机场接机
some groceries pick up a few books at the library books you're not buying at the library you are renting
一些杂货店在图书馆买了几本书 你不买的书 在你租借的图书馆
them renting books at the library so it doesn't mean buy although it can suggest buy.
他们在图书馆租书，所以虽然可以建议购买，但并不意味着购买。
This is very common very very common.
这很常见很常见。
OK.
好的。
And actually it's used much more often than buy and grab is used.
实际上，它的使用频率比购买和抓取的使用频率高得多。
These actually these three are used very much the same way.
实际上这三个的使用方式非常相似。
Hey I'm going to go to the supermarket.
嘿，我要去超市。
Oh really.
哦真的吗。
Could you Could you grab me a coke could you please grab me a Coke grab is probably more for buying
你能不能给我拿杯可乐你能不能给我拿杯可乐可能更适合买
stuff and getting stuff pickup is a little bit more common for people I think.
东西和取东西对我认为的人来说更常见一些。
So you you wouldn't as often say I need to grab my friend from the train station.
所以你不会经常说我需要从火车站抓我的朋友。
You'd probably say I need to pick up my friend from the train station.
你可能会说我需要从火车站接我的朋友。
Could you say get my friend from the train station or get my friend at the airport.
你能说从火车站接我的朋友还是在机场接我的朋友。
Yeah you definitely can.
是的，你绝对可以。
Could you get me a candy bar at the supermarket.
你能在超市给我买一个糖果棒吗？
Yes.
是的。
That's OK.
没关系。
I need to get some books at the library.
我需要去图书馆买些书。
Yes.
是的。
OK so generally speaking these three are very much the same.
好的，总的来说，这三个非常相似。
So now buy looks a little bit silly because it's so specific.
所以现在购买看起来有点傻，因为它太具体了。
And of course you can use it.
当然，您可以使用它。
I need to go buy some hairspray.
我要去买一些发胶。
I need to go buy some fruit.
我要去买些水果。
OK.
好的。
That's fine.
没关系。
But I really like to use these three because they can be used in so many other ways.
但我真的很喜欢使用这三个，因为它们可以用在很多其他方面。
We can't buy our friend at the airport.
我们不能在机场买我们的朋友。
That would be weird.
那会很奇怪。
We can't we can't generally buy our kids from school.
我们不能我们通常不能从学校买我们的孩子。
Or buy some books from the library.
或者去图书馆买些书。
No way.
没门。
So yeah this is fine but it's just more specific.
所以是的，这很好，但它更具体。
OK.
好的。
Now should we use pay for what we use pay for not to get stuff usually but if we have for example a
现在我们应该使用 pay for 我们使用 pay for 通常不是为了得到东西，但是如果我们有例如
bill a bill that we need to go out to pay I need to go to maybe the computer repair shop to pay for
账单我们需要出去支付 我可能需要去电脑维修店支付
the repair job that they did for me last week or I need to go to the maybe auto body shop to pay for
他们上周为我做的修理工作，否则我需要去也许汽车厂dy shop 支付
the work that they're doing on my car or to pay a bill.
他们在我的车上做的工作或支付账单。
OK whatever but this is just to give people money and it's usually not focused on getting some thing.
好吧，但这只是为了给人们钱，而且通常不专注于获得一些东西。
If we're getting something like it like candy or groceries or fruit we'll probably use these for.
如果我们得到类似糖果、杂货或水果之类的东西，我们可能会使用这些。
OK stop by means to go to a place for a short time.
OK 顺便去一个地方短暂停留。
I'm going to stop by my grandma's house and just say hi.
我要去我奶奶家打个招呼。
Now sometimes that could mean we're going to stay for a while.
现在有时这可能意味着我们要待一段时间。
Could be an hour or two.
可能是一两个小时。
Sometimes we do use it that way.
有时我们确实那样使用它。
Please please stop by any time that means come over anytime visit anytime.
请随时停下来，这意味着随时过来随时访问。
Maybe your friend says that hey stop by any time we can watch a movie.
也许你的朋友说，我们可以随时看电影，嘿嘿。
Whatever.
任何。
Stop by anytime.
随时停下来。
OK.
好的。
It's often used to describe something that happens in a short time but it can be used for something
它通常用于描述在短时间内发生的事情，但它可以用于某事
that happens longer.
这种情况发生的时间更长。
The more typical way to use this and the way I usually use it is when I am running errands.
更典型的使用方式和我通常使用的方式是在跑腿时。
I use stopped by to say where I need to go.
我用stopped by 来表示我需要去哪里。
I need to stop by the library to pick up a few books.
我需要去图书馆取几本书。
OK I need to stop by the library to pick up a few books.
好的，我需要去图书馆取几本书。
Now what about run to.
现在跑去怎么办。
I mean we need to run to a place.
我的意思是我们需要跑到一个地方。
No but it does give it a feeling of kind of being in a hurry going somewhere in a hurry.
不，但它确实给人一种匆忙赶往某个地方的感觉。
But it doesn't have to be.
但不一定是这样。
We often just use it to mean I need to go there.
我们经常只是用它来表示我需要去那里。
I need to go there but usually we use it when we're talking about the errands that we need to run.
我需要去那里，但通常我们在谈论我们需要运行的差事时使用它。
Listen to that.
听那个。
Running errands.
跑腿。
Are we running errands.
我们是不是在跑腿。
No.
不。
But there is a feeling of not going to a place and hanging out.
但是有一种不去一个地方，闲逛的感觉。
Not going to a shopping center and saying oh I don't know maybe I'll just walk around for three hours.
不会去购物中心说哦，我不知道，也许我会四处走走三个小时。
When we talk about an errand we usually have a clear purpose a direction a goal and usually time is
当我们谈论一项差事时，我们通常有一个明确的目的、方向和目标，通常时间是
a little bit tight.
有点紧。
Again it doesn't really mean we're running but it does have a feeling of OK.
同样，这并不意味着我们正在跑步，但它确实有一种好的感觉。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Let's do it and then let's leave.
让我们这样做，然后让我们离开。
We don't need to waste time.
我们不需要浪费时间。
For example I need to run to the coffee shop nearby to get some coffee beans because we're out.
例如，我需要跑到附近的咖啡店去买些咖啡豆，因为我们出去了。
It's a very common phrase by the way.
顺便说一句，这是一个非常常见的短语。
We're out for we're running low.
我们出局了，因为我们的电量不足。
That means we're almost out.
这意味着我们快要出局了。
We have none.
我们没有。
We're running low on coffee beans.
我们的咖啡豆快用完了。
I need to stop by the coffee shop.
我需要在咖啡店停下来。
I need to run to the coffee shop to grab some of those.
我需要跑到咖啡店去拿一些。
Because we're almost out.
因为我们快出去了。
So these phrases are all really common and we're going to see them in the example that we're going to
所以这些短语都很常见，我们将在接下来的示例中看到它们
look at now for running an errand and I'd like you to make sure next time you're describing your own
看看现在跑腿，我希望你确保下次你描述自己的
errands that you use these phrases because they're all super duper common.
您使用这些短语的差事，因为它们都是超级常见的。